CAMILLO ANGELOZZI

Address: 412-1 Jacksway Cres, London, Ontario N5X 3T5

E-mail: cangelozzi@gmail.com
Mobile Phone: 001 519-636-8255

GitHub: https://github.com/cangelozzi

Linkedin: https://hu.linkedin.com/in/camillo-angelozzi-a0b5a229

PERSONAL SUMMARY

Solid background in Problem Solving, Process Migration, and Data Administration; at the moment, developing strong skills in Web Development and Web Design. Recognizing the importance of Design and Coding knowledge, I have already gained experiences in Frontend and Backend projects. My learning path is continuously evolving toward new frameworks and libraries covering the technical side, the graphical aspect and the UI/UX interaction. Understanding the influence of Digital Media assets in various fields, my activities are also involving areas related to Blockchain and 3D environment. Overall, creativity and technology are my main focus and area of interest.

TECHNICAL SKILLS:

- Front-End Development with HTML/CSS/JavaScript.
- Debugging skills.
- Understanding of modern web practices.
- Knowledge of PHP / MySQL.
- Use of version control Git/GitHub.
- Back-End projects with MVC structures (Node/Express, Laravel).
- Practicing on Blockchain and Smart Contract development.
- Experience with test environments.
- Front-End library/frameworks (React / Vue).
- Adobe Creative Package and Cinema 4D.

PERSONAL SKILLS:

- Able to work individually or in a team.
- Clear and effective communication skills.
- Able to meet tight deadlines.
- High attention to details.
- Problem Solving experience.
- Willing to work and learn with emerging technologies.
- Interact clearly to both technical / non-technical audience.

EDUCATION

INTERACTIVE MEDIA DESIGN

Fanshawe College, London, ON, Canada; 2017 - 2019

BLOCKCHAIN DEVELOPER

Udacity Online Nanodegree SF, USA; 2018 - 2019

WEB DEVELOPER FULL STACK

Thinkful Online Bootcamp NY, USA; 2016 - 2017

TOURISM AND TRAVEL

Fanshawe College, London, ON, Canada; 1997 - 2000

WORK EXPERIENCE

REACTR – Fanshawe College

Backend Developer London, Ontario; Jan 2018 - now

SAFEGUARD INTERNATIONAL

INTERNATIONAL PAYROLL SPECIALIST Budapest, Hungary; 2016

APPLE Inc.

PAYMENT SPECIALIST (Temp) Cork, Ireland; 2016

UNISYS IT SOLUTIONS

BILLING, REPORTING and PROCUREMENT ANALYST Budapest, Hungary; 2011 - 2016

MORGAN STANLEY

ACCOUNT PAYABLE CONTROLLER TEAM LEADER Budapest, Hungary; Jersey City, NJ, USA; 2007 - 2010

MARSH & McLENNAN

ACCOUNT PAYABLE SUPERVISOR Budapest, Hungary; Witham, UK; 2006 - 2007

EXXON MOBIL

ACCOUNT PAYABLE ANALYST

Budapest, Hungary; Rome, Italy; Madrid, Spain; 2005 – 2006

GENERAL ELECTRIC COMMERCIAL FINANCE

CASH APPLICATOR SPECIALIST Budapest, Hungary; 2004 - 2005

CERTIFICATIONS

ITIL V3 Foundation certification; 2011, ITIL V3 Service Strategy Lifecycle certification; 2011